Keep breathing. Nice and slow.
保持呼吸 平稳而缓慢
Now, the first couple of shots will show you if the sights are off
最开始的几枪会告诉你是不是瞄准了
or the barrel's bent. Let me make this real easy for you.
- 或者射没射出子弹 - 我给你简单讲讲吧
The sights are off and the barrel's bent.
瞄准然后开枪
Mm, you're off to the left about an inch.
你往左边偏了一英寸
That's it. Shoot around the star.
就是这样 朝星星周围开枪
Not at it.
不要朝星星开枪
Yes! Yeah! You did it!
太棒了! 太棒了! 你做到了!
I didn't.
我没有
You just won your girlfriend a Teddy bear.
你刚给你女朋友赢了一只泰迪熊
Cool. Hey, which one you think she'd like best?
酷 嘿 你觉得她会最喜欢哪一个?
And then Thursday night, this physicist
周四晚上 这位物理学家
is giving a lecture in Brooklyn.
会在布鲁克林举办一场讲座
It's about time travel and the grandfather paradox.
是关于时光穿梭和祖父悖论的
I don't know if you're busy...
我不知道你那天有没有空...
Okay, Henry. Henry... Um...
好了 Henry Henry... 呃...
Can we talk for a second? Yeah.
- 我们能谈一谈吗? - 当然
I'm really happy that we've been hanging out so much.
我真的很高兴我们常常一起出来玩儿
Yeah, I- I like you too. Heh.
是的 我也喜欢你
Can you put down the bear?
你能把那只熊放下吗?
Henry...
Henry...
What?
怎么了?
I can't.
我不能
I know.
我知道
You have a girlfriend. It's just...
你有女朋友 只不过...
She never seems...
她似乎从来...
to want to do anything with you.
不想和你一起做任何事
Are you crying? No, I have allergies.
- 你在哭吗? - 没有 应该是过敏吧
I must just be, like, tearing up.
我一定流了很多眼泪吧
Henry, I think that's blood.
Henry 我觉得这是血
What? I-it...
什么? 我... 这...
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 豪斯医生  第八季第17集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 豪斯医生  第八季第17集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：ID 校对：ID 时间轴：绿
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：墨墨塔 FFlonestar 校对：酒囊饭袋喂蚊子去了 时间轴：绿
35-year-old male cries blood, and he's not vampire Bill.
35岁的男性眼睛流血 他又不是吸血鬼Bill
Go! Should we ask?
- 各抒己见吧! - 我们该问吗?
Nope! What, her?
- 不! - 什么 她吗?
Yeah, my favorite companion is retiring from "companning. "
我最喜欢的伴侣从这行退休了
So I'm interviewing replacements.
所以我在面试接替她的人
Thank you...
谢谢...
Butterscotch. Is that a family name?
Butterscotch 这是你的姓吗?
How long are you gonna be using the office for sex games?
你要用办公室干色情勾当到是什么时候?
Just so I can plan my day.
告诉我 我好为我以后的日子早作打算
Sex and work? I'm not a savage.
性和工作? 我又不是野蛮人
I asked for a cappuccino. That's what this is.
- 我要的是卡布奇诺 - 这个就是啊
No, a cappuccino's got a nice, stiff foam on it. This is wetter than...
不 卡布奇诺上面有漂亮浓厚的泡沫 这比那啥都要湿
Oh... almost slipped there.
哦... 差点就说走嘴了
Well, thank you, Ms. Scotch,
好吧 谢谢你 Scotch女士
but poor foaming's a deal breaker.
但是失败的泡沫很扫兴
Could you ask the next candidate to come in?
你能帮忙叫下个应聘者进来吗?
Initial exam showed no sign of trauma or subconjunctival hemorrhage.
初步检查显示没有外伤和结膜下出血的迹象
Lymphocytosis?
淋巴结胞增多症?
ALC's in normal range, but it's in the high end of normal.
绝对淋巴细胞计数在正常范围内 但马上就要超标了
Take a seat, Fawn.
请坐 Fawn
And tell me, what's your favorite Woody Allen movie?
告诉我 你最爱伍迪艾伦的哪部电影?
Annie Hall.
安妮・霍尔
You're interviewing hookers but not gonna talk to them about sex?
你在面试妓女 却不跟她们谈性事
Sex is a given. They're hookers.
性是必须的啊 她们是妓女
Defend your choice.
说说你的理由
It's the most popular. Ohh... that's so close.
- 这部是最流行的 - 哦... 你已经很接近正确答案了
We would have accepted, "Diane Keaton looks great in suits," or,
你可以说"黛安-基顿穿那身西装很漂亮" 或者
"it's a trenchant commentary on today's mores," or, "I needed the eggs. "
"这部电影是对如今道德的犀利的注脚" 或者是"我需要鸡蛋"
Thanks for your interest.
感谢你能过来
To get the gig, call girl- sorry, call woman-
要想得到这份工作 应召女生 抱歉 应召女郎
needs a combination of skills that I find useful/entertaining
得具备在我付钱的剩下的57分钟内
for the remaining 57 minutes of the hour I paid for.
让我觉得有用或有趣的技艺
Lymphocytosis works. Maybe we should take another look at the blood.
淋巴结胞增多症符合 也许我们应该再验下血
Could also be cavernous sinus thrombosis.
可能是海绵窦栓塞
Clot builds up pressure at the base of the brain.
血栓在大脑基底形成压力
Rerun the patient's blood panel and get a CT venogram of his head.
重新给病人验个血 再给他的大脑做个静脉造影
Let's see which one of you is right.
看看你们谁说的是对的
How are you with small appliance repair?
你擅长小家电维修吗?
Uh, this cavernous sinus thing, is it dangerous?
海绵窦这个病 危险吗?
If Henry's got it, we can treat it with a combo of drugs and surgery.
如果Henry得了这个病的话 我们可以用手术和药物结合加以治疗
Success rate is over 70%.
治愈率超过70%
Do you want me to call Amy again? No, it's fine.
- 你想让我再给Amy打个电话吗? - 不用了 没事的
Amy's his girlfriend. I'm the neighbor.
Amy是他的女朋友 我是他邻居
I did leave a message at their number. Do you wanna try her cell?
- 我给他们家电话留言了 - 你想试试打她的手机吗?
Be here for a few more hours at least.
你最少还要在这儿待好几个小时呢
Oh, she doesn't have one. She worries about radiation. I could stop by on my way home.
- 她没有手机 她担心被辐射 - 我可以回家的时候过去找她
She knows who I am, right? You don't need to, but thanks.
- 她知道我是谁 对吧? - 你不用去了 但还是谢谢你
Good luck. Okay.
- 祝你好运 - 好的
Have you ever paid for sex?
你找过妓女吗?
Every guy who's ever seen a Merchant Ivory movie has paid for sex.
每个看过Merchant Ivory电影的人都找过妓女
No. It just...
没有 我就是觉得...
seems too demeaning to women.
那么做对女人来说是种侮辱
Given the things you've done to women, that seems arbitrary.
考虑到你对女人们做的那些事 这看上去有些武断啊
You're Chi Park, right?
你是Chi Park 是吧?
Who's asking? Uh, you called about my guitar flyer.
- 你是谁? - 你打电话问我吉他的事情来着
You're Micah. This guy's selling
你是Micah 他在卖一把
a 1974 Gibson SG standard in tobacco for $1,250.
1974年的Gibson SG standard的吉他 只要1250块
Yeah, actually, I came in to tell you I already sold it.
没错 事实上 我过来是告诉你我已经卖出去了
Sorry.
对不起
Thanks anyway.
还是要谢谢你
Blood panel results seem pretty much the same as before, and that guy likes you.
验血结果跟上次基本一样 还有那男孩儿喜欢你
Maybe we should check for diabetes. Could weaken conjunctival vessels.
也许我们应该查查糖尿病 可能会让结膜血管壁变薄
And shut up. If I'm wrong, then why is he coming back?
- 还有不要瞎说 - 如果我说得不对的话 那他为什么要回来呢?
My band is rehearsing tomorrow night.
我的乐队明天晚上排练
You should come by and jam with us.
你应该过来跟我们一起玩玩
That... sounds fun.
这... 听上去很有趣
I'll think about it. Great. Call me.
- 我会考虑的 - 太好了 给我打电话哈
Park has a boyfriend.
Park有男朋友啦
I'll break your face.
我会打肿你的脸的
This is the talent portion of the interview. Okay.
- 这是面试中的才艺展示部分 - 好吧
You like cards.
你喜欢扑克牌
But you can juggle.
但是你要玩杂耍
I fail to see how this would be of benefit to you.
我看不出这个对你有什么好处
What if I'm busy? Have you got anything else?
要是我很忙怎么办? 你还会别的吗?
Sure.
是的
CT showed no clots or malformations.
CT显示没有血栓或者畸形
Park and Taub ruled out lymphocytosis and diabetes.
Park和Taub排除了淋巴细胞增多症和糖尿病
Well, since you have nothing of relevance to report,
既然你没什么重要的要汇报
I assume that you're here to toss your panties in the ring.
我想你来这是加入妓女应征大队的吧
Patient's got a mysterious girlfriend he really wants to see.
病人有一位他很想见到的神秘女友
She's unreachable by phone, and the neighbor's never even seen her.
打电话找不到她 邻居也从来没见过她
What do you think?
你怎么想?
He's gay.
他是个同性恋
I think he's a junkie. The girlfriend is a fix.
我认为他是个瘾君子 女朋友不过是个幌子
The guy's inhaling glue. Can you repair a blender?
- 这个人在吸毒 - 你会修搅拌机吗?
Can you bite me? Go search the patient's home.
- 麻烦你咬死我吧? - 去搜病人的家
Well, thank you, ladies.
女士们 谢谢你们
I've seen a lot of very talented candidates.
我看了很多非常有才华的应征者
Got a tough decision the next few days.
接下来的几天我需要做出一个艰难的决定
This is the part I hate.
这是我最讨厌的部分
Well... this is not exactly a crack den.
好吧... 这不像是一个吸毒者的窝
Doesn't exactly look like a woman lives here, either.
也不像是有女人住在这里
"To Amy. I love you. "
"给Amy 我爱你"
Okay. She exists.
好吧 至少她是存在的
Doesn't mean he's not a drug addict.
可这不意味着他不是瘾君子
It's good you're playing it cool with House. Once he gets a rise out of someone...
你能淡定应付House挺好的 一旦他惹恼别人...
Yeah, I'm not crazy about the whole hooker thing, but I get it.
是的 我对妓女这事儿虽然不热衷 但我能理解
Other than the fact that it's exploitative and dangerous for women,
除了这对女人来说是一种剥削 而且很危险
you get what you need without any of the emotional baggage.
你得到了你想要的东西 而且没有情感上的负担
You're not seeing anyone, I take it. I've been volunteering at the Trenton Free Clinic.
- 你没在和人谈恋爱 - 我一直在特伦顿的免费诊所做义工
Keeps me busy.
所以我一直很忙
You volunteer every night and every weekend?
你每天晚上 每周末都去吗?
No time to grab dinner? What's more important-
- 连吃饭的时间都没有吗? - 哪个更重要呢
making small talk over ravioli or helping people who are less fortunate?
吃饭的时候闲聊 还是帮助不幸中的人们呢?
With that rationale, none of us should ever eat again.
要是都这么想 那我们就都别吃饭了
Let's just say I'm not hungry right now.
那不如说我现在还不饿吧
Oh, God...
哦 天啊...
I don't think she's breathing. Do you think she OD'd?
我觉得她没在喘气啊 你觉得她是吸毒过量了吗?
That or he killed her. Pulse?
或者他杀了她 有脉搏吗?
No. I'll call the coroner.
- 没有 - 我给法医打电话
I don't think that's gonna be necessary.
我看没有这个必要
This one works in financial district. She can get tips, give you leg up in market.
这个人在金融领域工作 她可以给你建议 让你在股市如鱼得水
What is "fudgey Gonzalez"?
"fudgey Gonzalez"是什么意思?
Uh, imagine a "vanilla Gonzalez,"
想象下"白人版的Gonzalez"
but from the other side.
不过是指另一边
I'm about to make a decision, but there's still time for you to sneak under the wire.
我马上就要做决定了 但是还有一点时间让你来走走后门
My favorite Woody Allen movie is Melinda and Melinda.
我最爱的伍迪艾伦电影是"双生美莲达"
Our patient is not a junkie,
我们的病人不是瘾君子
but he does have a girlfriend.
但他确实有一个女朋友
I call her my "girlfriend" because people understand that.
我叫她"女朋友" 是因为这样人们会理解
If I explained it, they'd just think I was a weirdo.
如果我解释的话 他们会认为我是个怪人
We're not here to judge anyone's fetish. I'm not a pervert.
- 我们不是来评判别人的恋物癖的 - 我不是变态
It's not like I'm more attracted to dolls than humans.
不是说娃娃比真人更吸引我
So you don't have sex with her?
这么说你不跟她做爱喽?
It's not just about that.
她不仅仅是用来干那个的
Does the doll talk to you?
那娃娃还会跟你说话吗?
I know she's not a real person.
我知道她不是真人
In a lot of ways, she's better than a person.
可在很多方面 她比真人好得多
I can tell her things, and she won't argue with me or make fun of me.
我可以跟她说任何事情 她不会跟我争辩 也不会嘲笑我
I come home every night, and I know she'll be there waiting.
我每晚回家的时候 我知道她会在家里等我
So is your toaster.
你的烤面包机也是这样的
No one in the world has an emotional attachment to a toaster.
世界上没人会对烤面包机有情感依恋的
But a lot of people are willing to spend $7,000 on women like Amy.
但很多人愿意花七千块买一个像Amy这样的女人
Have you ever tried an actual- Yeah, I'm 35.
- 你尝试过真正的... - 是的 我都35了
I've been in relationships. Just none of them fulfilled me.
我也交过一些女朋友 但她们都不能满足我
And one day, I saw this website,
直到一天 我看到这个网站
and... maybe the perfect woman's out there somewhere,
也许 完美的女人就在这个世界的某个地方
but it's not worth going through
可是花那么大力气
what it would take to find her.
去找到她是不值得的
Amy makes me happy.
Amy让我快乐
You're swelling. It's sort of hot in here.
- 你在流汗 - 这里很热
Not that hot.
没有那么热
Bleeding plus two more symptoms: Fever and neurological.
出血加上两个多出来的症状 发烧和神经上的问题
I'm not sure about that last one.
我不确定最后那个算不算
I think he's just... weird. He wasn't hallucinating.
我觉得他只是... 很怪 他没有出现幻觉
He didn't have a thought disorder. And you don't think it's "disordered" to talk to-
- 他也没有思维失调 - 你不觉得这本身就是"失调"...
It's not all that different from talking to your cat or a Teddy bear.
这和你跟你家的猫或泰迪熊说话没有什么区别
You don't have sex with your cat or Teddy bear.
你又不会跟你家的猫或泰迪熊做爱啊
If you did, you'd probably talk to them more.
如果你做了的话 你可能会跟他们说更多的话
Guy loves an imaginary being who's never going to respond to him.
这人爱的是一个从没有回应过他的想象中的人
He's no crazier than millions of churchgoers.
他并不比上百万的基督徒更疯狂
You think anything off about any patient is a symptom.
你认为任何病人有任何的不正常就是一种症状
This guy buys flowers.
这个人买花
Real flowers for a piece of plastic in a dress.
给穿着衣服的塑料娃娃买真的花
You know what's really crazy?
你知道什么才算真的疯吗?
Living with a human being.
和人类住在一起
Someone with opinions and feelings.
一个有思想有感情的人
Gets mad just 'cause you want to take Salsa classes with them one night a week.
只是因为你想和他们每周一晚 去参加萨尔萨舞的课 就生气
One night. He's just running away.
- 一个晚上 - 他只不过是在逃避
He hangs out with a doll, he never needs to fear rejection.
他和娃娃在一起 他就从不会害怕被拒绝
It's sad. You do understand the irony here?
- 真伤感 - 你明白真正讽刺的是什么吗?
Every person in this room has a sex doll.
这屋子里的每个人都有一个性爱娃娃
At least the patient has the stones to be honest about it.
至少病人有胆量承认这件事
Ooh, a metaphor.
哦 隐喻啊
What you didn't foresee is that is that I actually do have a sex doll.
可惜你不知道的是我真的有一个性爱娃
Your doll is your kids.
你的娃娃是你的孩子们
Yours is your parents, yours is your charity.
你的是你父母 你的是你的慈善事业
All excuses for not being in a relationship. He's not wrong.
- 都是不肯发展一段感情的借口 - 他说得没错
And you- I have meaningless sex with random strangers.
- 而你... - 我和随机的陌生人做没意义的爱
Thanks for the insight, but I stopped that months ago.
多谢你的深刻见解 但我几个月前就不这么干了
I actually had a relationship. With a patient.
- 我事实上有过一段感情 - 和一个病人
You just date whoever happens to cross your path.
谁出现在你面前 你就跟谁约会
My dating is getting in the way of my dating? You don't go looking for the right person.
- 你是说我的约会妨碍了我的约会? - 你不会去找合适的人
You just shack up with whoever's in the room, and then you get surprised and/or divorced
谁在这屋子里 你就跟谁同居 然后你感到吃惊或者
when it doesn't work out. I'm surprised you haven't asked Adams out yet.
在事情无法挽回时离婚 我很惊讶你还没有跟Adams搞在一起
Uh, for your information, I've got a date tonight.
告诉你医生 我今晚有个约会
I'll be jamming with a cute guy and his band.
我要和一个可爱的小男生和他的乐队排练
- You'll bail. - He's right.
- 你会落跑 - 他说得对
The obvious solution is for me to hand my kids over to your parents.
对我来说最明显的解决方法 就是把孩子交给我的父母
Can we stop trying to argue the premise
我们能不讨论这些假设了吗
and move onto figuring out why it is that you're all social morons?
能继续探讨为什么你们都是社交白痴吗?
You do understand the irony here.
你得明白这里的讽刺
You mocking us for avoiding relationships,
你嘲笑我们逃避感情
but you can't handle losing your "doll. "
但是你都不能应对失去你的"娃娃"这件事
Your spending all this time and energy interviewing for a new one.
而是花了这么多时间和精力来招一个新的
You're right. That is stupid.
你说得对 那样做太蠢了
What about the patient?
那病人呢?
Dude's banging a sex doll.
这哥们跟性爱娃娃做爱
A festering cesspool of bodily fluids and associated bacteria.
娃娃里面都是恶臭的体液 细菌肯定少不了
Swab her out and find out which one.
给她做个化验 查查是哪一种
I need you. Please don't quit.
我需要你 求你不要离开我
You're the only hooker I know who can tune a piano.
你是我认识的唯一一个会调钢琴的妓女
If it's about the money,
如果是钱的问题
then I can up you to three nights a week.
那我可以一周增加到三个晚上
I'm getting married, House.
我要结婚了 House
His name's Harris.
他的名字是Harris
He's a certified accountant, he's loves schlocky horror movies,
他是一个有执照的会计师 他喜欢劣质的恐怖片
and he just moved in. We're very happy.
而且他刚搬进来 我们非常幸福
Well, you're happy? Yeah, you're happy because he doesn't know
你们幸福? 是啊 你们幸福是因为他不知道
about your employment history. He knows.
- 你以前是干什么的 - 他知道
We've talked about it, and he accepts me for who I am.
我们谈过这件事 他能接受真实的我
No. He...
不 他...
If he accepted who you were, he would not be making you give up your career.
如果他能接受你的过去 那他就不该逼你放弃你的事业
Women need their own identities, their own livelihoods.
女人需要她们自己的身份 她们自己的谋生手段
Otherwise, why was I smoking all those Virginia Slims?
不然我干嘛要抽掉那些弗吉尼亚牌女士香烟?
I know this is weird for you,
我知道这对你来说很奇怪
but you need to figure out a way to be okay with it.
但你需要想办法接受这个事实
I'll miss you, too.
我也会想你的
I feel like the stirrups are overkill.
我觉得这马镫有点夸张了
I've never done a pelvic on a doll before.
我以前从来没给娃娃做过妇检
I'm unfamiliar with the protocol.
我对操作流程完全不熟悉
I'm pretty skeeved out right now.
我快吐出来了
I'm not gonna lie. What House said back there-
- 实话实说 - House刚才说的那番话...
House says a lot of things. I don't just date whoever shows up.
- House说了很多话 - 我不是谁出现在我面前 我就跟谁约会
I mean, I did meet women in the hospital,
我是说 我确实在医院里遇到过一些女人
but they weren't just flings.
但我对她们不是玩玩儿而已
Basically, you're explaining why you're not going to ask me out.
基本上讲 你在解释你为什么没有约我出去
That's not what I was-
我不是...
did you want me to ask you out? Yeah.
- 你想让我约你出去吗? - 当然
I told Park to tell Taub to tell House to pass you that note.
我让Park告诉Taub告诉House来给你传话的
It's completely clean in there.
这里很干净
He said he just bathed her.
他说他会给她洗澡的
Adams...
Adams...
there's a swelling beneath the skin...
这里皮肤下有个肿块...
3- inch mass.
3英寸的肿块
Is it...
这是...
Part of the doll's skeleton? It feels like a tumor.
- 娃娃骨架的一部分吗? - 感觉像是肿瘤
CT showed an air-filled mass in the doll's abdomen.
CT显示娃娃的腹部有一个含气肿块
It's probably just a chemical reaction.
应该只是化学反应而已
Henry left her too close to a heating pipe or something.
Henry可能让她离热管道太近了
This guy brushes her hair every morning, brings home movies for them to watch together.
这家伙每天早上都给她梳头发 还会租电影回家来一起看
You think he tosses her in a broom closet at the end of each day?
你觉得他到晚上会把她塞进拖把间吗
More likely than it getting stomach cancer.
难不成它还会得胃癌啊
How about clostridium?
那梭菌呢
Bacteria got trapped in the airtight cavity, produced gas...
细菌被困在密封的腹腔里 产生气体
It doesn't explain the neurological issue.
这解释不了神经上的问题
We can explain that the same way we explain the tooth fairy.
这个问题可以用解释牙仙的方法来解释
Oh, I get to play Solomon. Cut the doll open.
我要学学所罗门 把这娃娃给劈成两半 (所罗门曾以此方法来判断孩子的生母)
We can't just destroy the patient's property. That thing cost 7 grand.
咱不能随便损坏病人的财产 那玩意儿要7千块呢
Exactly. Ask him for consent.
没错 去征求他的同意
If he says yes, then we get to go hunting bacteria.
如果他同意 咱就去抓细菌
If he says no, there's no need because he's crazy, and we need a different theory.
他要是不肯 那就用不着了 因为他疯了 那就另当别论了
See ya. Gotta go build a temple.
走了 鄙人要去修庙了 (所罗门王在耶路撒冷修庙)
Okay.
好吧
You sure? It won't be able to heal when we're done.
你确定? 这一动手可能就无法还原了
But you think she could tell you what's wrong with me.
但你们认为她能告诉你们 我出了什么问题
Yes.
是的
Okay.
好吧
Should we take her to the procedure room? It's not a her, which means we can do this anywhere.
- 我们要带她去手术室吗 - 她不是人 也就是说我们在哪儿都成
Adams...
Adams...
You can know something's not real and still love it.
有些东西 不是真的 但一样可以去爱的
I think the procedure room might be better for this.
我想去手术室或许更好
You are a horrible person.
你真是个坏人
All I need is to break up one marriage.
我不过是要拆散一段婚姻罢了
You've broken up three of your own.
你自己不就拆散过三段
You're like the Stephen Hawking of killing relationships.
你就是"爱情杀手"界的史蒂芬霍金
Actually, no, Stephen Hawking is the Stephen Hawking of-
不对 史蒂芬-霍金是史蒂芬-霍金....
Okay. I have work to do. Your computer is off.
- 好吧 我还有事 - 你电脑都没开
Sorry, I can't hear you over my "stereo. "
不好意思 我的立体声听不到你讲话
Why do you assume that marriage is better than hooking?
你为什么觉得这段婚姻会好过瞎搞呢
We don't know anything about the guy. He could be a serial killer.
我们对此人一无所知 说不定他是连环杀手呢
Even if that were true, it would still be a toss-up.
就算是如此 几率也是一半一半
What kind of guy marries a hooker? Somebody who hires hookers.
什么样的男人会娶一个妓女呢 一个花钱找妓女的人
And someone who hires hookers is not exactly the monogamous type.
而花钱找妓女的人 并不是会对婚姻专一的类型
If we expose him as a cheater... You're a coward.
- 如果咱揭发他有偷腥的话 - 你真没种
Would a coward fight to the end to save a damsel in soon-to-be-proved distress?
没种的人会抗争到底 拯救一个将要陷于水深火热的姑娘吗
Absolutely, if what he's afraid of is other damsels.
没错 如果他害怕的是其他姑娘的话
Your last relationship failed so miserably, you ended up in jail.
你的上一段感情失败得一塌糊涂 最终让你进了大牢
Now you're clinging to this hooker
现在你却粘着这个妓女不放
when there are about 3 billion other women out there who aren't call girls,
明明还有其他30亿的女性 不是应召女郎
some of whom are attractive and intelligent,
其中更是不乏迷人有智慧的
one of whom is living in your apartment and is married to you!
有一个还就住在你家 嫁给了你
You're right.
你说得对
Why am I asking you for help?
我干嘛要找你帮忙呢
You shouldn't sleep with Chase.
你不应该跟Chase上床
Thank, God. You got here just in time.
谢天谢地 你来的正是时候
What do you have against him?
你讨厌他什么啊
Nothing, but House has a way of getting into people's heads.
啥都没有  但是House总有办法钻进你的脑袋里
Just like last week when he was prying into your relationship with Chase?
就像上周他打探你和Chase的关系?
It was silly then, and it's silly now.
当时觉得很蠢 现在也一样蠢
Why was it silly then?
当时为什么觉得蠢
I'm not 5'9" with curves and flowing hair,
我不是5'9"高 前挺后翘 一头秀发
so it's impossible for me to get it on with a good-looking guy?
所以就不可能有帅哥对我动心 是吗
Wow. Do you resent me?
你生我气吗
You're the quirky, hardworking sophomore
你是任性又用功的好学生
and I'm the evil cheerleader who steals boys?
而我是专门抢男人的邪恶啦啦队长?
If you're not getting any, it's not my fault.
你没人爱 又不是我的错
Should we get the one with the panda on it or the bird?
咱们是要上面有熊猫的 还是小鸟的呢
Good choice.
真有眼光
Pandas eat only bamboo,
熊猫只吃竹子
they know nothing about cereal.
对麦片一无所知
Your little girl is adorable.
你女儿真可爱
Thanks. She keeps me very busy.
谢谢 她让我忙得不可开交
You and her mom must be very proud.
你和她妈妈一定很骄傲吧
Her mother... Died in childbirth.
她妈妈...分娩的时候死了
*You ask me if there'll come a time *
*You ask me if there'll come a time *
*when I grow tired of you *
*when I grow tired of you *
*never my love *
*never my love *
*never my love never my love *
*never my love never my love *
*how can you think love will end *
*how can you think love will end *
*when I've asked you to spend *
*when I've asked you to spend *
*your whole life *
*your whole life *
Amy. How'd it go?
Amy 怎么样啊
We're growing cultures now,
我们在做培养菌了
but she looked clean, and there was no telltale smell.
不过她看起来没问题 没有明显的气味
I'm guessing the lump was just an air bubble that got trapped in the mold.
我想肿块只是模子里有个气泡而已
You bandaged her up. I threw in some stitches, too.
- 你给她包扎了 - 还缝了几针呢
Just wanted to make her look her best.
想让她看起来美美的
Do you want me to put her in her chair?
要我把她放在椅子上吗
Henry?
Henry?
Call a code!
呼叫急救
You looking at the apartment with those or the transit of Mercury?
你是用这个看对面公寓 还是观测水星凌日啊 (天文现象)
If night comes, you'll be thanking me.
到了晚上 你就会感谢我了
They're seeking heat. He's an accountant.
- 这是红外热像的 - 他是个会计
How late do you think he's going to party? I bought jar to pee in.
- 你以为他能折腾到多晚? - 我买了罐子撒尿
Yeah. We heard crackles in Henry's lungs.
- 说 - 我们在Henry的肺部听到有杂音
We diuresed him, but he still needs oxygen. Echo shows normal heart function.
- 我们有让他排尿 但他还是需要吸氧 - 超声波显示心脏功能正常
Could be high output failure from anemia.
可能是贫血造成的高输出衰竭
Hematocrit was rock normal. What is this? Mushroom?
- 血细胞比容也很正常 - 这是什么 蘑菇吗
Say "mushroom," charge $2.
说"蘑菇" 两块
Say "truffle," charge $5.
说"块菌" 5块
Is that the man who wants to marry hooker?
那个就是和妓女结婚的男人?
Probably. But he's not the one we're after.
可能是 不过咱们要盯的不是他
Should we ask? Nope. Oh!
- 咱要问问吗 - 不用
How rude of me not to situate you. I'm doing Emily a favor.
我居然没跟你们报备 真是太失礼了 我在帮Emily一个忙
We're going to track her fiance
我们在跟踪她未婚夫
until Dominika can seduce and expose him as the lying cheater I need him to be.
直到Dominika能够引诱他 照我想的那样 揭发他这个满口谎言的负心汉
I'm guessing she didn't ask for this favor.
我看这不是她主动找你帮忙的吧
Oh, you know, the noblest gifts are the ones we give anonymously.
你也知道 最高尚的礼物都是匿名的
Crackles are nonspecific.
杂音的来源还不清楚
Hypoxia plus bleeding could indicate D.I.C. or some other-
组织缺氧加上出血可能是D.I.C. 或者其他 (散播性血管内凝血)
no neurological symptoms?
没有神经上的症状?
I knew your bleeding heart would bring you around.
我就知道心软会让你醒悟的
Too bad it's also taking you off the market. And by market, I mean Chase.
很遗憾也让你没了市场 市场我指的是Chase
Come on, buck up, Chase.
别 打起精神来嘛 Chase
There's always Park. Unless...
还有Park在嘛 除非...
How did band practice go?
乐队排练如何?
- Great. - Does she look like she's lying?
- 很好啊 - 她看起来像在说谎吗
Kind of.
挺像的
Popo needed a ride to the doctor, and my mom couldn't, so-
婆婆需要有人载她去看医生 妈妈没空 所以...
You're terrified of dating because...
你害怕约会 因为...
a previous relationship ended because your latent rage
前一段感情结束 都是因为你潜在的愤怒
made you vicious in arguments. Or-
让你很毒舌好斗 或者是...
Or reincarnation. In a past life, she was Anne Boleyn.
或者是投胎转世 上辈子她是Anne Boleyn(英格兰王后)
Interesting.
有意思
Taub feels confident enough to turn the spotlight on himself.
Taub信心十足 把重点转移到自己身上
It's almost as if he wants me to ask...
几乎等于他想让我开口问...
What's her name? Wendy Jacobson.
- 敢问小姐芳名啊 - Wendy Jacobson
33, Brown grad, family therapist. Nice choice.
- 33岁 布朗毕业 家庭治疗师 - 不错啊
Since you got two families to "therapize. "
因为你有两个家庭要"治疗"
First date, we didn't discuss everything important-
第一次约会 我们没有聊什么重要的
So it was just a one-night stand.
那就是一夜情喽
You're wrong. I actually like her. I'm going to see her again.
你错了 我还真挺喜欢她的 我还会和她再见面的
Mazel tov.
好运啊
Great relationships often start with snap decisions aimed at proving me wrong.
成功的感情都是 从为了证明我是错的草率决定开始的
Air bubble in the doll could mean the silicone is degrading.
娃娃体内的气泡可能是硅树脂退化了
If he hailed some particles...
如果他有吸入什么微粒
Silicone deposition. That could work.
硅树脂沉积 这个或许有可能
Start him on plasmapheresis.
开始给他用血浆去除法
Now, turning to Adams, my theory is tripartite-
现在转回Adams 我的理论分为三部分
Want to hear my thesis? It's kind of interesting.
想听听我的命题吗 挺有趣的呢
No man comes out.
没有男人出来
But old naked lady in 3-C is eating whole block of cheese.
不过3-C的裸体老太太 把一大块奶酪都给吃了
Will this hurt?
会疼吗
No, you might feel a little cold, though.
不会 或许会觉得有点冷
Crap.
见鬼
I only have a second, but I went to the time travel lecture.
我时间不多 不过我去听了时光穿梭讲座
That is... awesome.
真是...太棒了
What is it?
这是什么啊
It's so...
好...
Oh, realistic.
真实
Oh, and it's all bandaged up.
绑了绷带啊
It is one of those CPR things?
这是用来练习CPR的吗
No.
不是
We're starting a procedure. A little privacy-
我们要做个手术 请回避...
No, no, it's- it's good that she's here.
不 不用 她在这儿没事的
Molly,
Molly
I'd like you to meet Amy.
我想让你认识一下Amy
What?
什么?
I'm serious.
我是认真的
I know it seems a little strange,
我知道这看起来有点怪
but she means a lot to me.
但这对我来说意义很大
I, um, got to get back to work.
我 呃 得回去工作了
But you just got here. Sit down. Yeah, but I-
- 你才刚来呀 坐下嘛 - 可是我...
I said that I only had a second.
我刚说了我时间不多的
Enjoy the handouts.
希望你喜欢那些资料哟
Listen, um, I have to admit something.
那个 我想跟你坦白一下
Okay.
好啊
Her mom isn't dead. We're separated.
她妈妈没死 我们只是分居了
You're the first person I've asked out since then.
而你是我在那之后第一个约会的人
I'm not used to explaining... I panicked.
我不善于解释...我当时慌神了
Which I regret, because now that I've gotten to know you,
而我现在很后悔 因为我渐渐了解你了之后
I like you.
就喜欢上了你
It was a really stupid lie.
我撒了个愚蠢的谎
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Was that a different baby?
这不是上次那个孩子吧
No...
不是啊...
That was a different baby.
这明明是另外一个孩子
It's nice having you here.
有你在这儿多好啊
I wish you could come over and get in bed with me.
我好希望你能过来和我躺在一起
Like this?
像这样吗?
You're talking? It's not all I can do.
- 你说话了? - 我会做的可不止这些哟
Amy, there are doctors...
Amy 这儿有医生...
I don't know.
我不知道....
Just put your hands on me.
把手放在我身上就好
It hurts. It hurts...
好痛...好痛...
Pushing Lorazepam.
注入劳拉西泮
If it wasn't neurological before, it sure is now.
如果之前没有神经症状 那现在一定有了
Right upper quadrant's distended.
右上腹肿胀
He's hallucinating because his liver's failing.
他产生幻觉是因为他的肝脏不行了
Elevated transaminases confirm liver failure.
转氨酶指标升高也显示了肝脏衰竭
We'll have to put him on the transplant list in a couple days.
过几天我们就得把他放上等待移植名单
It's clearly not the silicone. Could be vasculitis.
肯定不是硅胶的问题了 血管炎
Serologies were negative.
血清无异常
Yeah, if you want Adams to hear,
你如果想让Adams听得清楚
you might want to not stand so conspicuously far away.
就别故意站那么远嘛
I'm making coffee.
我在煮咖啡
And sometimes, I date co-workers. Like everyone else on the planet.
有时候我是和同事约会 就像这地球上的其他人一样
Hepatic fibrosis.
肝脏纤维化
If it damaged his platelets, it'd explain the bleeding.
如果他的血小板被破坏 就能解释出血
Unexpected. I actually thought you might agree with my theory.
真没想到哟 我还以为你会同意我的理论呢
Because that would mean nothing's your fault.
因为那样就意味着你完全没错了
You fell into relationships based on proximity. Of course they failed.
你选择伴侣的首要条件是距离的话 那感情生活失败也在意料之中
But I guess I was wrong.
不过我想我还是说的不对
You picked perfect women. You just screwed it up.
你选的女人个个都完美 总是搞砸的是你自己
How about all five of us live together and the $7,000 sex doll?
咱五个和那七千块的充气娃娃搬一起住算了呗
It'll solve all our hang-ups. $7,000?
- 啥问题就都解决了 - 七千块钱？
Adams suggests that we all sleep together,
Adams都提议大家群居了
and your issue is high prices? Pretty sure she was joking.
- 你能提出的问题就是那娃娃多少钱? - 我挺确定人家是开玩笑的
Yes, I'm 99% sure that you're right, but I would never forgive myself-
是哦 我觉得你有99%的可能是对的 但是如果有那么百分之一的希望
Those dolls are only $5,000.
这种娃娃只卖五千块钱
He must have had it customized somehow.
他这个肯定有特别定制过
Oh, like, you didn't check the website?
别装的跟你没上过那网站一样
I guess we don't need to ask how your dating life is going. I was curious.
- 看来我们不用问你的感情生活情况如何了 - 好奇不行吗
Hepatic fibrosis wouldn't cause difficulty breathing.
肝脏纤维化不会导致呼吸困难
It would if liver failure opened pulmonary av shunts.
如果肝衰竭使得肺部血液循环无法进行的话就会了
Fibrosis fits.
纤维化符合症状
Start the patient on steroids and find out how he pimped his ride.
给病人上类固醇 然后去查查他定制什么了
Why?
为什么?
Because I don't know the answer.
因为我不知道答案呗
Foosball? Can't. Marriage to destroy.
- 来玩桌上足球么? - 没空 忙着破坏婚姻呢
Okay...
好呗...
"Okay" as in passive-aggressive reverse psychology?
"好呗"? 这是被动攻击式的反转心理学呢
Or as in depressed resignation
还是灰头土脸式的投降认命?
"okay" as in I changed my mind.
"好呗"就是说我改变主意了
Expand.
给个解释
Oh, it's morally reprehensible and bound to fail,
是啊 你做的事情是道德败坏并且必然会失败的
but in a weird way, it's a step forward. This thing with Emily.
但在某个奇怪的方面 这也是向前的一小步啊 Emily的这件事
Contract. It's real without being real.
- 快别说了 - 这是件没意义的有意义的事
It's a long-term relationship that can't actually hurt you.
一段不会伤害到你的长久关系
It's, um... a stepping stone. It means you want more.
这算是...铺路石吧 说明你还想追求更多
So, passive-aggressive reverse psychology.
那么就是被动攻击式的反转心理学咯
Got it.
早说呗
Try not to come on too strong, okay?
别太明显了 知道吧?
Just get to know him a little. Ease into it.
先侦察敌情 慢慢深入
Why would I ease? True.
- 我还慢个什么劲啊 - 没错
You could just walk up and stick your hand down his pants,
你是可以直接走上去就拉人家裤子拉链
but I heard there's a middle step. Men want to have sex.
- 但我可听说那不是第一步哟 - 男人就想要乱搞
Not with crazy people.
但不是和疯子
Well, yes, a lot with crazy people, but not that kind of crazy.
是 大部分时间是和疯子乱搞 但不是这种疯子啊
Well, yeah, that kind of crazy-
好吧 是和这种疯子-
They don't care how crazy if she look like me.
长得像我这样 多疯都无所谓
Okay. Easing.
好吧 还是慢慢来哟
I'm Jennifer, new to marketing department.
我是Jennifer 市场部新来的
Harris. Accounts receivable. Oh, interesting.
- Harris 应收账款部 - 真有趣
Do you want to get out of here and have sex?
你想出去乱搞一下吗?
Uh, sure.
好呀
You know, I got 45 minutes left on my lunch break.
我午休时间还剩四十五分钟呢
Mm-hmm. Where you wanna go?
想去哪里?
Off to a place where men don't cheat on the women they love.
去一个男人不背叛女人的地方
You're not invited, obviously.
而你显然是不会受到邀请的
Cheating? What are you talking about?
背叛? 你在说什么?
Why, I hope you're speaking
哎哟 我希望你说这话
out of some deep kind of moral relativism because-
是出于某种深刻的相对论 因为-
Who are you people?
你们是谁啊?
You're not Emily's fiance.
你不是Emily的未婚夫
Emily's my sister.
Emily是我妹妹
We called the company that made Amy.
我们给制作Amy的公司打了电话
They said they modeled her after some photos you sent them.
他们说她是根据你发给他们的照片定制的
Who is she?
她是谁呢?
We met last Christmas.
我们上个圣诞节认识的
She's a yoga instructor.
她是个瑜伽教练
Totally different from me.
和我完全不同
She-she loved Chopin, hated Indian food.
她...喜欢卓别林 讨厌印度菜
She changed entire my life for 17 weeks.
17周里 她彻底改变了我的生活
My husband cheated on me...
我的丈夫背叛了我...
With a girl he met on the plane coming back from our honeymoon.
对象是一个他在我们蜜月返程飞机上认识的女人
It's not easy to get past things like that.
这样的事情总是让人难以接受
She wasn't unfaithful. She didn't betray me.
她并没有不忠 也没有背叛我
She just... she just wasn't in love with me.
她只是...她只是从没有爱上过我
I know Amy's not going to break your heart.
我知道Amy永远不会伤我的心
But she's also not going to change your life.
但她也永远无法改变你的生活
The lights are bright.
灯好亮啊
Sorry. What's happening to me?
抱歉 我是怎么了?
Is your neck stiff? Yeah.
- 你感觉脖子僵硬吗? - 是的
I think you have meningitis.
我觉得你可能得了脑膜炎
I'm not leaving the business.
我并不是不做这一行了
I'm just leaving you.
我只是不想再见到你了
I didn't want you to feel bad. So let me get this straight.
- 我只是不想让你难过 - 于是事情是这样的
I'm being dumped by a hooker...
我被一只鸡甩了...
Who's worried about my feelings? You're married.
- 这鸡还关心起我的感受来了? - 你已经结婚了
Half your clients are married. And you're a hooker.
你有一半的顾客都结婚了 而你是做鸡的
My other guys sneak around,
我其他的顾客都是偷吃
but you'll take me into the bedroom while your wife's in the next room.
但你当着你老婆的面就把我往卧室里领
That's just... mean.
这可...太残忍了
Oh, my God. The marriage, it's a sham.
我的天哟 这个婚姻就是个骗局
The only really thing about it is the green card
唯一真的就是她最后
she's going to get at the end of it.
拿到的那张绿卡
So, if you want to get the meter running... It's still mean.
- 所以 如果你想要现在开始计费... - 反正还是很残忍
It's not a marriage. It's a felony.
这不是婚姻好吗 这是诈骗罪
I've seen how she looks at you when you're together. Trust me.
我见过你们在一起时她看你的眼神 相信我
She likes you.
她喜欢你
And I've seen how you look at her.
而且我也看到过你看她的眼神
Fever's up 105. He's not responding to meds.
高烧105度 对药物没有反应
At this rate, he'll be dead by the time we get the cultures back.
照这个速度 我们拿到细菌培养实验的结果之前他就会死
Spinal fluid was full of white cells.
脊髓液中全是白细胞
Meningitis could be carcinomatous. Cytology showed nothing.
- 脑膜炎可能已经癌变 - 细胞分析未显示病状
An amoebic infection would cause fever and meningitis.
阿米巴变形虫感染可能导致高烧与脑膜炎
But not liver failure. It could if he had a clot.
- 但不会引起肝衰竭 - 如果他同时还有血栓的话就会了
How could amoebas get past his cribriform plate?
可阿米巴变形虫是怎么通过他的血脑屏障的呢?
He went swimming in a frozen lake in New Jersey?
他在新泽西能找到一个冰湖游泳吗?
Adams said his ex-girlfriend was a yoga instructor. Maybe he sprained his chakras.
- Adams说过他的前女友是瑜伽教练 - 他可能练瑜伽的时候拉伤了什么脉轮
Yoga nuts are way more likely to be into alternative medicine.
瑜伽狂热者更可能求助于非正统医学
He has this little weird teapot in his house.
他家里有一个奇怪的小茶壶
What was it like?
什么样的?
Um, little. Weird. Teapot-ish.
就是小的 奇奇怪怪的 长得像茶壶
Like that? Yeah.
- 就那样的? - 是啊
You think he drinks some sort of toxic herbal tea? Yes...
- 你觉得他喝了什么有毒的草本茶? - 没错
If by "tea," you mean salted tap water.
如果你这"茶"指的是加盐的自来水
And by "drink," you mean poured up his nose.
"喝"指的是把水灌进他的鼻孔里的话
His girlfriend didn't just leave him with a broken heart.
他的女朋友不仅给他留下了一颗破碎的心
She left him with a neti pot. It's an Indian method of.
还给她留下了一个长颈壶 而这在印度
Of clearing the sinuses during allergy season.
是在过敏多发季节用来清理鼻腔的
Also known as now.
而这过敏多发季节正是当下
The distilled water can act as a snot flushing system.
纯净水当然可以作为冲洗系统
With tap water, it can act as an amoeba delivery system
但是自来水呢 就会变成阿米巴变形虫输送系统
to the fluids around the brain. Start him on metronidazole.
直达脑脊液 给他上甲硝唑
If he's lucky, he'll get to see
如果他够幸运 他还能活到
his plastic children walk down the aisle.
他的塑料娃给他打酱油的那一天
My neck feels much better.
我的脖子感觉好多了
Your fever's gone, and your liver function's almost back to normal.
你的烧退了 肝功能也恢复正常了
You should be able to go home soon. I'm going to have some hospital bills to pay.
- 很快就可以出院了 - 这次的医药费可不少啊
I don't suppose used sex dolls go for anything online.
估计二手充气娃娃在网上也卖不了几个钱吧
Dr. Adams?
Adams医生
Can I get your email?
能给我你的email地址吗?
What for?
做什么用?
I just thought maybe we could see each other again.
我觉得我们还可以再见见面
I- I can't. No, I know.
- 我...我不能 - 我知道
It's a professionalism thing, but you won't be my doctor when I get out of here.
这是有关职业道德的事情 但我出院之后你就不是我的医生了
It's not that. It's- what is it?
- 不是那样的 是... - 是什么?
You said I should change my life. You were talking about yourself, too.
你说我应该改变自己的生活 你也是在说你自己
I know you were. Henry, I- I think you should ask Molly out.
- 我知道你是的 - Henry 你应该约Molly出去
I should have known this would happen.
我就知道会这样
You're a good guy, Henry.
你是个好人 Henry
You deserve more than a doll.
你值得拥有比一个娃娃好得多的生活
Promise me you'll keep trying.
向我保证你会继续尝试
Okay.
好的
Date tonight?
晚上有约会?
So she can't deal. There's someone out there who can.
就算她接受不了 接受得了的女人这世上多得是
You just got to find her.
你只要找到她就好了嘛
I'd love to prove House wrong,but...
我挺想证明House说得不对的
I ruined my marriage,
但是...我已经毁掉了我的婚姻
broke two people's hearts, had two kids who are always
伤了两个人的心 有了两个
going to wonder why I didn't love their mommy enough.
会永远想不通我为什么不够爱她们妈咪的孩子
It's better if I just... focus on what I do have.
我真的不如...还是着眼于我现有的一切吧
Give that band guy a call.
给那个玩乐队的家伙打电话
I'm not that good at guitar.
我吉他弹得不好
Or flirting or small talk.
也不会调情或者闲聊
I'm not as pretty as Adams,
我不像Adams那么漂亮
I have stuffy clothes, and I hate my hair.
我的衣服都肥肥大大 而且我讨厌自己的发型
Adams works 80 hours a week fixing bunions on hobos
Adams每周工作80小时给流浪汉治灰指甲
because she can't face getting to know someone new.
是因为她无法面对新的生活 认识新的人
Trust me.
相信我
You find a boyfriend, she'll be the jealous one.
如果你恋爱了 她会嫉妒你的
See you tomorrow.
明天见
Do you...
你想...
want to get a drink?
出去喝一杯吗?
To annoy Park or to prove House wrong?
是想让Park不高兴呢 还是想证明House是错的?
Oh, I... It's just, um...
哦 这个...我...
I think it's time for a change.
只是觉得该是时候改变了
I don't really think that's a good idea for me right now.
我可不觉得这对我来说是个好主意
House has a way of getting in people's heads.
House总有办法钻进你的思想里
Yeah. Yeah.
是啊
No, mom. I'm still at work.
没有 妈妈 我还在上班呢
I'll be home in a couple hours.
几个小时之后才能回去
Love you too.
我也爱你
Ready?
准备好了吗?
One, two, three, four.
一 二 三 四
*they say we're young and we don't know *
*they say we're young and we don't know *
*we won't find out until we grow *
*we won't find out until we grow *
*well, I don't know if all that's true *
*well, I don't know if all that's true *
*'cause you got me and baby I got you *
*'cause you got me and baby I got you *
*babe *
*babe *
*I got you babe *
*I got you babe *
*they say our love won't pay the rent *
*they say our love won't pay the rent *
*before it's earned, our money's all been spent *
*before it's earned, our money's all been spent *
(dear MRS HOUSE:????) *I guess that's so, we don't have a pot *
*I guess that's so, we don't have a pot * (House夫人 永久居住权申请获得批准)
*at least I'm sure of all the things we got *
*at least I'm sure of all the things we got *
*babe *
*babe *
*I got you babe *
*I got you babe *
*I got flowers in the spring */i>
*I got flowers in the spring *
*I got you to wear my ring *
*I got you to wear my ring *
*and when I'm sad you're a clown *
*and when I'm sad you're a clown *
I fix blender.
我修好搅拌机啦
So I see.
发现了
I had fun seducing hooker's fake fiance.
勾引妓女的假未婚夫有趣的
Sorry it didn't work.
抱歉没成功哈
Yeah, I thought I'd take a break
是哦 我觉得我还是
from the whole hooker thing.
把这妓女的事情停一停
I think maybe you need milk shake.
我觉得你可能需要一杯奶昔
Is pistachio.
开心果味的哟
*I got you babe *
*I got you babe *
I'm... gonna go to bed. See you tomorrow.
我...要去睡觉了 明天见
*hold my hand *
*hold my hand *
*I got you to understand *
*I got you to understand *
*I got you to walk with me *
*I got you to walk with me *
*I got you to talk with me *
*I got you to talk with me *
*I got you, I won't let go *
*I got you, I won't let go *
*I got you to love me so *
*I got you to love me so *
*babe *
*babe *
*I got you babe *
*I got you babe *
*I got you babe I got you babe *
*I got you babe I got you babe *
*I got you babe
*I got you babe
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入